Lucky gun
Brought to you by: Ko-Fi.me/OrangeFlash
i'm coming!
Ouch!
Who the hell is it?
I'd thought I could come over there to play with you. But sorry, I won't be coming.
You can forget about it.
Shizuka-chan?
Oh, no! Hello?
She rejected me?
And to think that, I had saved yesterday's cake for Shizuka-chan, just for her!
I'll eat it all by myself!
Oh no, it's all bad luck for me today!
Oh my, sorry.
That's my cake!
Sorry, but we have a guest and this cake is all we have for now.
How can you do that?
Today is not my day, I want to read my Manga.
Where are my Manga that I had put on the table?
Daddy took them so that he can read them while riding on train.
Oh no!
How unlucky I'm today!
Yeah, perhaps.
Say, do you have any gadget to change my luck?
Well, Not... Maybe yes...
Why are you pointing that gun towards me?
Revolver with four consecutive bullets.
There are 3 reds and 1 black bullet in total.
Load them up and spin it....
If you were shot by a red bullet, you'll have good luck for the entire day.
Really?
However, if you were shot bythe black bullet, your entire day will be unlucky.
How come?
Doraemon, why don't you please put that black bullet away?
That doesn't work.
If bullets are not loaded together, they won't work.
Besides, you can't get any good luck without risk.
That's too selfish!
Plus red bullets are 3X more than the black bullet.
3X, huh?
Alright, let's try it out!
What's wrong? Pull the trigger quickly.
i can't do it! I'm so afraid!
That's it! Let's try it out on someone else!
Doraemon!
Please don't...
See you later.
Bye.
Mum!
What?
Pull the trigger like this!
If it's red bullet, then it's good luck.
But if it's black bullet, your luck on that day won't be good.
That sounds like fun!
You can try the first shot.
Really? But that sounds scary.
Don't worry.
You're usually very careful with everything.
Let me have a try then!
So...
Suddenly, I feel very good.
It seems to be red one
Oh, no, a red bullet is down.
Ms. Nobi!
I forgot very important thing.
I've brought you some souvenir from when I went to travel overseas.
Thank you!
See? I had told you before!
I'm not scared at all!
Oh, no.
I always feel it's a black bullet.
So it is.
Men have to be bold.
Bold?
I've got an idea!
Good!
Wait.
Let's use the black bullet first on someone else...
Then I can reliably shoot it!
Let me play, let me play.
I love this kind of game the most.
I have to say first.
There's a remaining black bullet which brings bad luck.
You think I'm scared to try this?
The black bullet will probably fire!
It's a red bullet!
Feeling very good and very happy!
Giant, shall I take you for a movie today?
Yes, thanks Daddy! Let's go!
See you later.
Oh, I got the circle
I envy Giant, I should've tried it before giving to him.
There's still 1 red shot, remember?
Try it boldly.
No, this time it's black bullet that will be shot.
It's impossible that all three red bullets would be fired in sequence.
Suneo-kun, you talk too much!
Do you want to feel extraordinarily lucky?
If a red bullet is shot, then you'll have good luck for an entire day.
But if the black bullet is shot, You'll have bad luck for the entire day.
Then...
What's the matter with you girls? All of you are so timid!
You should talk...
Well, girls! I'll do it to prove that I'm a man!
Suneo, can you do it?
I am pulling the trigger.
It'll be a black bullet now!
Oh, no! It's the remaining red bullet!
Suneo is actually so bold.
I am sorry. Let's go and play together.
It was your fault that there's only but the black bullet is what remains!
This revolver sucks!
You didn't have to just throw it away like that!
It's a gun!
I want to shoot!
Don't point it at me! Stop it!
Don't run away. I'll shoot!
Let's hide here!
That boy thinks we're playing with him.
We don't have good luck!
Found ya!
I want to shoot!
Don't ...
Nothing good will happen with me for the next 24 hours!
You always bully him!
Pay for it!
Here, ¥3,000.
All our savings for the whole year is gone in water!
Being hasty will only bring back luck!
let's be careful and go home!
Or so I thought...
Oh, no!
Guess we're unlucky for the day!
Be careful ...
Oh, my god
Let's consider today as a day of bad luck and then forget all about it!
But that doesn't make me feel better.